Mark Sunhurov

Junior Software Engineer





Summary

Motivated junior embedded software engineer with background in scientific area. Has been actively working on his pet projects (for example see [1, 2]) for the last two years. Initially tutored by a mentor who has 10 years of experience in Linux kernel and embedded development. Has expertise in developing the MCU firmwares and Linux applications in C, knows basic concepts of embedded system design, Git workflow, able to read schematics and use electronic tools. Looking for a job in embedded area, preferably in Linux environment. Considers moving to another city.

Experience

May Intern, SQUAD, DPD Streaming, Lviv.

- 2022-present Bug fixing
 - Unit testing

2010–2022 Research fellow, KIPT, Kharkiv.

- Participance in the international project on applied superconductivity with Brookhaven National Laboratory
- Conducting research on some stages of the institution research program as
- Performing analytical calculations

Education

2020 PhD degree, Kharkiv Institute of Physics and Technology NAS Ukraine Speciality: Solid-state physics

2005–2010 Master's degree, V. N. Karazin Kharkiv National University, Kharkiv. Speciality: Physics

Computer skills

Languages C, Bash

Platforms ARM32, x86, STM32

Tools GCC, GDB, Make, Git, Vim

OS Linux

Languages

Ukrainian Fluent

My native language

Russian Fluent

My native language

English Intermediate

Speaking, reading and writing

References

- [1] https://github.com/Mark-271/kitchen-clock-poc
- [2] https://github.com/Mark-271/cpu-usage-tracker